Broadcast Center Recordings, circa 1980-2017: Finding Aid AC362
University Archives
Broadcast Center Recordings
circa 1980-2016
University Archives
Princeton University. Library. Special Collections
Princeton University. Office of Information Technology. Broadcast Center.
AC362
74 boxes
760 items
The Broadcast Center operates a full TV/audio production studio and supports recording of events, classes, and interviews at the studio and on campus. The collection includes over 2,300 video recordings of Princeton-related lectures, conferences, symposia, events, ceremonies and creative works.
Scope and Contents
The collection includes over 2,300 video recordings of Princeton-related lectures, conferences, symposia, events, ceremonies and creative works. These recordings feature a variety of speakers, including politicians, celebrities, and activists, as well as scholars and professors from Princeton and around the world. Topics include religion, finance, gender, technology, philosophy, science, sports, and other issues. Also included is a series of Campus Shots, which capture daily life at Princeton, documenting various activities on campus.
Conditions Governing Access
The collection is open for research use.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Access to recordings follows Mudd Manuscript Library policy for preservation and access to audiovisual materials. This collection contains both analog and digital collections.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Transferred to the University Archives in 2009, 2010 [AR.2009.130], 2013 [AR.2013.103], 2014 [AR.2014.107], 2016 [AR.2016.055], 2017 [AR.2019.095], and 2019 [AR.2019.009].
Appraisal
No materials were separated from this collection during processing in 2016 or 2019. No prior information about appraisal is available.
Princeton University. Office of Information Technology. Broadcast Center.
Biographical / Historical
The Broadcast Center operates a full TV/audio production studio and supports recording of events, classes, and interviews at the studio and on campus. Previous to its establishement in 2008, Media Services performed this role. Established in 1984, Media Services expanded on the responsibilities of the Audio-Visual Center.
Rites and ceremonies -- New Jersey -- Princeton.; Education, Higher -- New Jersey.; Lectures.; Audiovisual materials.; VHS (TM).; Betacam (TM).; Betacam-SP.; DVDs.; Born digital.; Princeton University Faculty.; Princeton University Students.; Princeton University. Office of Information Technology. Broadcast Center.
- Series 1: Broadcast Center Recordings, undated; 37 boxes
  Conditions Governing Access
  The collection is open for research use.
  Scope and Contents
  Includes video recordings of Princeton-related lectures, conferences, symposia, events, ceremonies and creative works. The media that these videos were stored on did not indicate the date of recording.
  Arrangement
  No arrangement scheme has been imposed on this series.
  - U.R.C. - The art of the ask, undated; 1008; 1 box (Box 1)
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
    3/4"
  - College preview, undated; 1032; 1 box (Box 1)
  - Princeton vs. Yale Football, undated; 1084; 1 box (Box 1)
    Film Transfer
  - Princeton: A search for answers, undated; 1235; 1 box (Box 1)
    Backup DVD Made
  - Conversations That Matter, undated; 1790; 1 box (Box 1)
    1992 CASE Gold Medal Produced by Andrew Greenspan and Associates
  - The quality of teaching at Princeton, undated; 1005; 1 box (Box 2)
  - Athletics Slide Show, undated; 1168; 1 box (Box 2)
    Princeton Sports
  - The eminent chemist videotapes series, undated; 1022; 1 box (Box 3)
    Dr. Hubert N. Alyea
  - Princeton Resident Colleges promo, undated; 1033; 1 box (Box 4)
    Michael Beahan
  - The enduring commitment, undated; 1034; 1 box (Box 4)
  - The Bell Curve, undated; 1129; 1 box (Box 4)
    VHS
  - Lecture, undated; 1131; 1 box (Box 4)
    Jim Baker
  - Grad./Alumni, undated; 1178; 1 box (Box 4)
    A-10 Jadwin Tape 1. April 23
  - Interview, undated; 1200; 1 box (Box 4)
    Toni Morrison Interview With Bill Moyer
  - Princeton: A search for answers, undated; 1205; 1 box (Box 4)
  - Lecture, undated; 1223; 1 box (Box 4)
    James Carville
  - Lecture, undated; 1226; 1 box (Box 4)
    Mike Mahoney
  - Atomic Power, undated; 1672; 1 box (Box 4)
    1940's BandW film/Life and Time joint venture
  - A Simulation of the National Economic Commission, undated; 1036; 1 box (Box 5)
    Spring '89 Tape #2
  - Princeton University Molecular Biology Promo Spot, undated; 1040; 1 box (Box 5)
    Produced for Mike Beahan
  - Video Segment, undated; 1051; 1 box (Box 5)
    Bill Bowman: The ice pond: Rolling with nature. Evening magazine feature segment with Ted Taylor, Robert Socolow, and Don Kirkpatrick
  - Lecture, undated; 1167; 1 box (Box 5)
    Merce Cunningham
  - Princeton/Stanford, undated; 1177; 1 box (Box 5)
    Delta Queen 1990
  - PPPL - TFTR, undated; 1218; 1 box (Box 5)
    Harry Bush Dub from 3/4'' - crane and wide shots
  - MLK day, undated; 3; 1 box (Box 6)
  - Doo Wop 50, undated; 17; 1 box (Box 6)
  - Symposium, undated; 42; 1 box (Box 7)
    DAT
    Adlai Stevenson
  - Arriflex, undated; 43; 1 box (Box 7)
  - Looking back: Reflections of black Princeton alumni, undated; 113; 1 box (Box 11)
    Hi-8
  - Cover Shots, undated; 125; 1 box (Box 11)
    President Bush. Landing and taking off cover shots
  - Iranian documentary, undated; 129; 1 box (Box 11)
    16mm transfer
  - Lecture, undated; 130; 1 box (Box 11)
    James Stewart
  - Conversations that matter, undated; 136; 1 box (Box 11)
    Princeton at 250
  - The year of the Tiger, undated; 139; 1 box (Box 11)
    Alumni council of Princeton Basketball documentary from Bradley days
  - Lecture, undated; 154; 1 box (Box 11)
    Laurie Date is listed as 2/27 with no year
  - Conversations that matter, undated; 192; 1 box (Box 11)
    No date
  - Lecture, undated; 194; 1 box (Box 11)
    Dennunzio No date given
  - Open House, undated; 200; 1 box (Box 11)
    1990 date
  - Riverside, undated; 201; 1 box (Box 11)
    Only 1 tape, tape #2, no date
  - Language Lab, undated; 213; 1 box (Box 12)
    no date given
  - Computer Science footage, undated; 218; 1 box (Box 12)
  - Campus gargoyle footage, undated; 220; 1 box (Box 12)
  - 2 hour French programming, undated; 221; 1 box (Box 12)
  - French class, undated; 223; 1 box (Box 12)
    Nick Morgan No date
  - Swimming photographs, undated; 226; 1 box (Box 12)
  - French commercials - Canadian channel, undated; 228; 1 box (Box 12)
  - Lecture, undated; 234; 1 box (Box 12)
    Rodger Ladd
  - CIT Films, undated; 240; 1 box (Box 12)
    Roger and Kath
  - Woodrow Wilson School, undated; 371; 1 box (Box 14)
    DVCam
    Migration and Development/Latin American Studies/Woodrow Wilson School Symposium - "Beyond Smoke and Mirrors"
  - Renaissance Series, undated; 407; 1 box (Box 15)
    (Don is viewing for correct data entry)
  - Madison Program, undated; 423; 1 box (Box 15)
    National Sovereignty and International Institutions
  - Lecture, undated; 430; 1 box (Box 15)
    Democracy In Post-Occupation Iraq: Values, History, Structure 3 Panels/3 Tapes
  - Going Metric: A one time change, undated; 1001; 1 box (Box 23)
    no date
  - Friends of swimming, undated; 1009; 1 box (Box 23)
  - Good Morning America - E-Quad, undated; 1014; 1 box (Box 23)
  - TigerNet sample tape - Staff '90, undated; 1029; 1 box (Box 24)
  - A Simulation of the National Economics Commission, undated; 1035; 1 box (Box 24)
    Spring '89 Tape #1
  - Athletics Slide Show, undated; 1038; 1 box (Box 24)
    Spring '90
  - Annual Giving Slide Show, undated; 1039; 1 box (Box 24)
  - Meet The Press - Adlai E. Stevenson, undated; 1056; 1 box (Box 24)
  - Princeton: A search for answers, undated; 1091; 1 box (Box 24)
    1973
  - College Previews: Princeton, undated; 1096; 1 box (Box 24)
  - Lecture, undated; 1097; 1 box (Box 24)
    James Baker III: Policy address on Soviet Union
  - Tell someone, undated; 1098; 1 box (Box 24)
    Student version
  - A Simulation of the National Economic Commission, undated; 1104; 1 box (Box 25)
    Spring 1989
  - Tell someone, undated; 1105; 1 box (Box 25)
    Staff Version
  - A return to Princeton, undated; 1113; 1 box (Box 25)
  - Lecture, undated; 1120; 1 box (Box 25)
    Alyea: Lucky Accidents and the prepared mind Fall 1985.
  - Conus, undated; 1122; 1 box (Box 25)
    BetaCam
    Youth. Purple numbered slides
  - Dedication lecture, undated; 1123; 1 box (Box 25)
    CJL
  - Lecture, undated; 1126; 1 box (Box 25)
    Benazir Bhutto 35 minutes: Broadcast version
  - Tell Someone!, undated; 1143; 1 box (Box 26)
    Staff Version 15:13
  - Lecture, undated; 1163; 1 box (Box 28)
    Alyea: Lucky Accidents, Great Discoveries, and the Prepared Mind. 1981.
  - National Archives, undated; 1171; 1 box (Box 28)
    3/4" SP
    International Film Foundation Affiliated Film Producers
  - Lecture, undated; 1172; 1 box (Box 28)
    Betacam SP
    Brubeck
  - Lecture, undated; 1173; 1 box (Box 28)
    Brubeck Tape #1
  - Lecture, undated; 1174; 1 box (Box 28)
    Brubeck Tape #2
  - Smithsonian Statue for Princeton, undated; 1186; 1 box (Box 29)
  - 1991 Class Day, undated; 1187; 1 box (Box 29)
  - Princeton Class of '55, undated; 1188; 1 box (Box 29)
    Bill Boloen
  - Princeton University Football Halftime Promotion, undated; 1210; 1 box (Box 29)
    3:30 spot
  - Princeton University Football Halftime Promotion, undated; 1211; 1 box (Box 29)
  - Princeton With One Accord, undated; 1231; 1 box (Box 30)
    Edited version Starts with Jay Sherrard
  - Conversations That Matter, undated; 1233; 1 box (Box 30)
    Dub from 1"
  - Campus Footage, undated; 1234; 1 box (Box 30)
    Early morning (Fall) Nassau Hall and East Pyne
  - Evolution of the Campus, undated; 1251; 1 box (Box 31)
    250th Anniversary
  - Okie Album, undated; 1266; 1 box (Box 31)
    Professor Howarth
  - Roundtable Class on Racism, undated; 1283; 1 box (Box 32)
    BetaCam SP
  - Campus Shots (Spring), undated; 1285; 1 box (Box 32)
    Students walking, tight shot of buildings, long shot of students conversing, cars on campus
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1294; 1 box (Box 32)
    Nell Painter - AAS lecture
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1304; 1 box (Box 32)
    Students conversing indoors and playing Foozball, Sydney's film class
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1305; 1 box (Box 32)
    Sydney's film class
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1306; 1 box (Box 32)
    Sydney's film class, interview with students outside of class
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1311; 1 box (Box 32)
    Firestone interior, interviews with students
  - Campus Shots (Fall), undated; 1313; 1 box (Box 32)
    Adults and children playing football, interviews
  - Campus Shots (Fall), undated; 1316; 1 box (Box 32)
    Crew team at dawn, interview by Carnegie Lake, student reading Goat Boy by the Chapel, interview with student reading it
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1329; 1 box (Box 32)
    Alexander Nehamas, basketball practice with Carril - pep talk to team
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1330; 1 box (Box 32)
    Basketball practice with coach Carril, students eating at night with candles outdoors
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1333; 1 box (Box 32)
    Small # of students at McCosh 50 conversing
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1334; 1 box (Box 32)
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1337; 1 box (Box 32)
    Students eating at the Annex
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1340; 1 box (Box 32)
    Students conversing at a roundtable
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1341; 1 box (Box 32)
    Students conversing
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1345; 1 box (Box 33)
    Departmental dinner/conversing
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1351; 1 box (Box 33)
    Roundtable class (unknown lecturer)
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1362; 1 box (Box 33)
    Unknown lecturer at Comp. Sci. 104, after lecture discussions, student/prof. conversing over lunch, students discussing philosophical issues over lunch
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1366; 1 box (Box 33)
    Alumni P-Parade
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1367; 1 box (Box 33)
    Alumni interviews
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1368; 1 box (Box 33)
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1369; 1 box (Box 33)
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1370; 1 box (Box 33)
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1371; 1 box (Box 33)
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1372; 1 box (Box 33)
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1374; 1 box (Box 33)
    Alumni hanging out talking with one another, cover shots of Princetonian from the 50's, reunion cover shots: band playing/people dancing
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1375; 1 box (Box 33)
    Reunions: cover shots, band playing/people dancing, alumni interview
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1376; 1 box (Box 33)
    Alumni interviews, interview with Ralph Nader
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1377; 1 box (Box 33)
    Ralph Nader interview, P-Rade
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1378; 1 box (Box 33)
    P-Rade
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1379; 1 box (Box 33)
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1380; 1 box (Box 33)
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1381; 1 box (Box 33)
    Alumni interviews, Richardson interior cover shots/classical concert going on
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1382; 1 box (Box 33)
    Richardson interior cover shots with classical concert going on
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1383; 1 box (Box 33)
    Classical concert at Richardson with cover shots
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1384; 1 box (Box 33)
    Classical concert at Richardson
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1402; 1 box (Box 34)
    Interview with Cornel West, Cornel West helping student with a question
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1428; 1 box (Box 35)
    Prof. Littman - robotics lab, students conversing while eating, Prof. Wilkinson - lab/students interviewed
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1429; 1 box (Box 35)
    Students interviewed about their interest in Physics, interview with professor Wilkinson, John Flemming and student conversing
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1430; 1 box (Box 35)
    John Flemming and student conversing
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1431; 1 box (Box 35)
    John Flemming interview, student being interviewed while walking
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1432; 1 box (Box 35)
    Interview with student while walking, theater class/run through with audience cover shots (unknown prof.)
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1433; 1 box (Box 35)
    Theater class/unknown prof.
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1434; 1 box (Box 35)
    Theater class/run through/audience cover shots
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1435; 1 box (Box 35)
    Theater class with unknown prof., after class conversations bet/ prof. and students, interview with theater students
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1436; 1 box (Box 35)
    Prof. Peter Brown interviewed
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1437; 1 box (Box 35)
    Prof. Peter Brown interviewed, flower cover shots, Prospect House cover shots
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1438; 1 box (Box 35)
    Cornel West class lecture
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1439; 1 box (Box 35)
    Cornel West lecture
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1440; 1 box (Box 35)
    Cornel West class lecture/after class questions, Witherspoon st. cover shots,
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1441; 1 box (Box 35)
    Outside interview with student
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1443; 1 box (Box 35)
    Indoor Chapel shots, outdoor interview with student,
  - Campus Shots (Spring), undated; 1444; 1 box (Box 35)
    Squirrel shot for Steve, students reading and walking outdoors, student studying at Firestone, Firestone indoor cover shots
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1445; 1 box (Box 35)
    Student interviewed, a few shots of BandW pictures from WW2 Poland
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1446; 1 box (Box 35)
    John Flemming - Weif Coothoo + part of John Franklin (Says Princeton University - Conversations that matter) - Documentary
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1447; 1 box (Box 35)
    John Franklin to end
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1449; 1 box (Box 35)
    Weif Coothoo (Says Princeton University - Conversations that matter) - Documentary
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1450; 1 box (Box 35)
    Title shot of Conversations That Matter
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1451; 1 box (Box 35)
    Q and A of a lecture, shots of still photography from Victorian era and the Polish Ghetto
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1515; 1 box (Box 35)
    Aerial shots
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1516; 1 box (Box 35)
    WW school fountain, Spring '88
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1517; 1 box (Box 35)
    Material Science - Navrotsky/Lampert Calorimeter - Reel 1
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1518; 1 box (Box 35)
    Material Science - Microscope Lampert Int - Reel 2
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1530; 1 box (Box 36)
    Chapel interior shots, overhead student shot (eating/studying), student on sofa reading, students eating and conversing
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1531; 1 box (Box 36)
    Classroom and Visitors Plaza
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1532; 1 box (Box 36)
    Students getting pizza from Victors, students eating pizza and conversing, Firestone interior/exterior, interior of Princeton U store with students
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1533; 1 box (Box 36)
    Richardson exterior, coach Carril interview, tight shot of books, Walter Noeller (Glee Club)
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1534; 1 box (Box 36)
    Glee club office, student answering phone and working
  - Campus Shots (Spring), undated; 1535; 1 box (Box 36)
    Trees and flowers in bloom - dorm shots, people walking, tight flower shots, women's crew shots - spring '88
  - Campus Shots (Spring), undated; 1536; 1 box (Box 36)
    Graduate school exterior shots in the rain, tight shots of pillars, Nassau Hall clock tower, Richardson exteriors, Firestone exterior shots, People walking around near McCosh, tight shot of masonry Swan and Tiger, flower shots at Prospect Garden
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1537; 1 box (Box 36)
    Crew team on Carnegie Lake(overcast), women's choir under arch
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1545; 1 box (Box 36)
    Econ Building cutaways
  - Various shots from books and slides, undated; 1565; 1 box (Box 37)
  - Conus Washington, undated; 1566; 1 box (Box 37)
    Gunfire, songs, and fireworks at Princeton University
  - Tiger Video, undated; 1604; 1 box (Box 38)
    Reunions - Alumni singing, alumni couple with baby interviewed, lunch/Princeton band at Dillon
  - Tiger Video, undated; 1605; 1 box (Box 38)
    Reunions - P-Rade: People walking around, interview with alumni, 1962, people parading
  - Tiger Video, undated; 1606; 1 box (Box 38)
    Reunions - P-Rade: People getting into the large field: 1962, balloons go in the air, 1921, 1922, 1918, 1919, 1917, 1918, audience cover shots, 1923, 1924, 1925, 1926, 1927, 1928, 1929, 1930, 1931, 1932, 1933, 1934
  - Tiger Video, undated; 1607; 1 box (Box 38)
    Reunions - P-Rade: airplane carrying banner for 1962 class, people marching, 1939, 1941, 1942 (Mariachi band), 1943, 1945, 1947, 1948, 1949, 1950, 1951, 1952, 1953, 1954, 1955, 1956, 1957
  - Tiger Video, undated; 1608; 1 box (Box 38)
    Reunions - P-Rade: Large field: Balloons in the air, audience, 1959, 1963, 1967, 1969, 1970, 1971, 1972, 1973, 1974, 1975, 1977
  - Tiger Video, undated; 1609; 1 box (Box 38)
    Reunions - P-Rade: Marching onto field, 1977, 1947, alumni shaking hands with Bill Bowen, alumni at podium giving speech, exterior club shots
  - Tiger Video, undated; 1610; 1 box (Box 38)
    Reunions - exterior club shots, alumni interviewed, class of 1967 having dinner, guitar and organ grinder, food tight shots
  - Tiger Video, undated; 1611; 1 box (Box 38)
    Reunions - God's eye of alumni eating, WPRB on air shots, 1967 bulb sign at night, live outdoor band at night, 1957 bulb sign at night
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1624; 1 box (Box 38)
    Students walking near Prospect gate, Murry Dodge interior shooting an outdoor class through window, outdoor class, students coming out of McCosh, students walking, Picasso sculpture/museum shot, students eating outside, arch/student shot, shooting into d
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1654; 1 box (Box 39)
    Ice blocks brought in to middle of campus, student choir under arch, student interviews
  - Computer Screen, undated; 1661; 1 box (Box 39)
    Early computer graphics technology at work
  - Looking Back: Reflections of Black Princeton Alumni, undated; 1671; 1 box (Box 39)
    75 min.
  - Huntley/Brinkley News footage from May 1970 - Vietnam War, undated; 1675; 1 box (Box 40)
    Huntley/Brinkley
  - Dance Concert, undated; 1676; 1 box (Box 40)
  - Campus Footage, undated; 1677; 1 box (Box 40)
    Nassau Hall, arch shot with Richardson in background, Richardson Hall exterior, students on grass, Wu Hall interior/exterior, students eating/conversing, Firestone exterior, gargoyles, Chapel, WWS fountain, Carnegie Lake, Lacross practice,Bowen Hall exterior
  - CBS News Archives, undated; 1678; 1 box (Box 40)
    Princeton University
  - 250th Anniversary of Princeton University, undated; 1680; 1 box (Box 40)
    Formal award ceremony winners 1979+1993
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1682; 1 box (Box 40)
    Choir singing under arch
  - Princeton University's 250th Anniversary Celebration, undated; 1684; 1 box (Box 40)
    Cover Shots: Princeton University/Coke machine being setup, registration, ice block preparation, interview with ice crew worker, alumni interview
  - Charter Day, undated; 1686; 1 box (Box 40)
    Tape 1 Satellite
  - Princeton Commencement, undated; 1687; 1 box (Box 40)
    Lecture Series Eisenhauer and Minitz
  - Fireworks, undated; 1689; 1 box (Box 40)
  - Raab Renaissance, undated; 1690; 1 box (Box 40)
    Raab - Scientist original negative
  - Princeton Slides, undated; 1693; 1 box (Box 40)
    Green 1-20 Various Princeton University shots-present/archival - people/pins/canoeing on Carnegie
  - Princeton History, undated; 1697; 1 box (Box 40)
    S. Georgia Nugent Pagano/Juliano
  - Princeton History, undated; 1717; 1 box (Box 41)
    Interview - Massie. B-Roll and interview - Artie. Maher/Juliano
  - Princeton History, undated; 1719; 1 box (Box 41)
    Piano/Ping Pong, President Shapiro's Student Seminar Maher/Juliano
  - Princeton History, undated; 1720; 1 box (Box 41)
    President Shapiro's Student Seminar Maher/Juliano
  - Princeton History, undated; 1721; 1 box (Box 41)
  - Princeton History, undated; 1722; 1 box (Box 41)
  - Princeton History, undated; 1723; 1 box (Box 41)
  - Tiger Video, undated; 1754; 1 box (Box 41)
    Firestone interior/exterior cover shots
  - Looking Back, undated; 1773; 1 box (Box 42)
    SVHS
    Reflections of black Princeton alumni
  - Princeton with one accord, undated; 1776; 1 box (Box 42)
    one
  - Princeton University archival slides, undated; 1777; 1 box (Box 42)
    labeled - Princeton IMC red slides
  - Centennial Public Lecture Series opening tags, undated; 1783; 1 box (Box 42)
  - Centennial Public Lecture Series closing tags, undated; 1784; 1 box (Box 42)
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1452; 1 box (Box 43)
    Katz Interview - Star of College Preview interview
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1453; 1 box (Box 43)
    Students in arch near Holden Hall, inside Rockefeller dining Hall
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1454; 1 box (Box 43)
    Bowen - class lecture, shots of students
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1455; 1 box (Box 43)
    Ultimate Frisbee, Lacrosse game
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1475; 1 box (Box 44)
    Downtown Princeton, Traffic, Firestone exterior, interview with student, Frisbee
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1476; 1 box (Box 44)
    Ultimate Frisbee, tennis practice, students leaving practice, lacross practice, pickup basketball, cheerleading practice, students under arch singing Prince,
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1477; 1 box (Box 44)
    Student choir under arch with audience cover shots, students walking around, band playing outside with cover shots
  - Campus Shots, undated; 1478; 1 box (Box 44)
    Students playing cards/pool and drinking in bar, st. cover shots from top of building, campus shots from top of building, WPRP DJ on air with cover shots